excaliberpc.com 2019-04-29

# Security & Privacy Policy | EXcaliberPC.com

At EXcaliberPC.com, your privacy and security is of utmost importance to us and we are fully committed to protecting it. We do not trade or sell your information to any other third party. We use your personal information we collect to customize our site for a more personalized shopping experience and for order processing. From time to time, we also monitor customer traffic and usage patterns but only on aggregate and without any identity specific data.

## Mailing List

If you have signed up for our mailing list, we only need an email address and we send only information that you have requested. Under no circumstances is your email address shared with any other company.

## Privacy Policy

When you place your order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, billing address for your credit card, credit card number, and expiration date. Your IP address is also recorded for security purposes. We need these information so that we can verify your order and to process it quickly and to send you pertinent status on your order. We require you to submit a user name and password of your choice for future access to your orders and information. Your user name and password is to remain confidential and you should not share it with anyone.

By using our website, you agree for EXcaliberPC.com to collect your information and consistent in the privacy policy stated manner. If we deem it necessary to alter our privacy policy, the updated policy shall be posted on this page. EXcaliberPC.com is a California Corporation and shall abide by all local, state and federal laws. If required by law, we shall disclose any personal information to the proper authorities. In addition, account information may be released when we believe its release is necessary to enforce the terms of sale or to protect our rights or property or those of our customers. We would also actively report any illegal actvity related to our website our use of our site. If you have additional questions, please email [support@EXcaliberPC.com](mailto:support@EXcaliberPC.com)

## SSL Data Encryption

EXcaliberPC.com takes every precaution to protect our clients' personal information. Your information is protected both online and offline. EXcaliberPC.com uses the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. We use the most advanced 128bit encryption technology offered by Verisign. Offline access is limited to employees with the proper security clearance to access customer orders and their data.
